《断头谷》前情提要
Previously on Sleepy Hollow.
珍妮弗・米尔斯  你以前帮过你姐姐
Jennifer Mills, you've helped your sister before.
艾比说这件事你能帮上忙  所以她让我找你
Abbie wants me to bring you into this, says you'll be valuable.
但是我需要知道
But I need to know--
-你是帮我们还是不帮  -帮
- are you in or out? - In.
你坠入爱河  然后结婚
You fell in love, you get married,
但你却完全不知道
but the whole time you have no idea
你的妻子是个女巫吗
that your wife is a witch.
正是如此
Correct.
-你怎么会不知道呢  -她在保护我
- How could you not know? - She was protecting me.
我们是古老骑士修道会的一员  立誓对抗
We are part of an ancient order sworn to fight the darkness
断头谷中的黑暗势力
that hides in Sleepy Hollow.
我们面对的是我们远不能控制的力量
We're dealing with forces so beyond our control.
远远不能
Beyond beyond.
珍妮
Jenny!
这就是关键  中尉
That's the key, Lieutenant.
现在  我们更加
Now, more than ever,
需要卡特里娜了
we need Katrina.
你有什么不敢说的
What is it you're afraid to say?
我知道我为什么会在这里
I believe I know why I am here.
-为什么  -伊卡伯德
- Why? - Ichabod!
我的车正缓缓驶近那儿
I'm pulling up to it right now.
对  我会给你发照片
Yes, I'll send you pictures.
简直不敢相信它曾属于我的家族
I can't believe it used to belong to my family.
我知道  我就是很好奇
I know. I'm just so curious.
我想尽我所能了解这里的一切
I want to learn everything I can about this place.
这是附近最古老的一座宅院
It's one of the oldest homes in the area.
我花了五年才把地契搞定
It took me five years to secure the title.
我想让它恢复旧时的光辉
Oh, I'd like to restore it to its original grandeur.
我们还有好多工作要完成
We have a lot of work to do.
我爱它
I love it.
真的吗
Really?
这是历史  山姆  准确地说是我家族的历史
It's history, Sam-- my family's history, to be exact--
所以放尊重点
so show some respect.
发生在这里的事应该被铭记
Things happened here that need to be remembered.
看着像鬼屋
Looks haunted.
作为保镖而言  你算够胆小的了
For a bodyguard, you are a very fearful man.
莉娜  莉娜
Lena. Lena!
在知道这房子结构没问题前  你不能...
Until we know it's structurally safe in there, you are not go...
太棒了
It's amazing.
我们该把一切都恢复原样
We should restore all of this.
这些顽固的破树枝
Stubborn little brutes.
山姆  我们应该带把修枝剪来的
Sam! We should've brought the hedge clippers!
这地方完完全全地...
The place is completely...
我只是想指出一日三餐的传统已经消失殆尽
I'm merely noting the eradication of a thrice-daily tradition,
再没人好好腾出时间来吃顿饭了
wherein each meal is treated with the proper allowance of time.
倒不是说驾车外带就没给我留下深刻印象
Not that the "Drive-through" wasn't impressive.
而且虽然餐馆起了那个名
And despite this establishment's nomenclature,
这可跟我吃过的苏格兰菜不一样
this resembles no Scottish meal I've ever eaten.
就说这些  是来自奥地利统治期的荷兰
These are from the Austrian Netherlands, for one thing.
还做得很糟糕
And dreadfully prepared.
我们的感恩节估计就这样了
This is probably as much of a Thanksgiving as we're getting.
你妹妹怎么办
What about your sister?
这可是家庭团聚时刻
This is "Family time."
虽说自打她从精神病院出院就由我当监护人
I don't think my having conservatorship over her
可我不觉得这就意味着接下来会演变成
since her release from the nuthouse necessarily leads
在餐桌上互递红莓酱的温情场面
to "Pass the cranberry sauce."
递什么
The what?
火鸡  红莓酱  南瓜馅饼
Turkey, cranberry sauce, pumpkin pie.
指1620年搭乘五月花号移居美国的英国清教徒
就是清教徒吃的那些东西
You know, all the stuff the Pilgrims ate.
那些清教徒连做酱的糖都没有
The Pilgrims didn't have any sugar to make a sauce,
更别说馅饼了
let alone a pie.
而且吃的是鹿肉
And venison,
不是火鸡
not turkey, was served.
哪怕能有只饿得半死的野鸡
It would've been a miracle for a single half-starved
-在寒冬里出现就是奇迹  -等下
- pheasant to trot past during such a harsh winter... - Hold up.
野鸡
Pheasants?
一提到节日
All this talk of holidays,
火鸡和家庭时光
turkeys, family time...
就让我平添烦恼
irks me.
是因为卡特里娜
Because of Katrina.
如果我不能和妻子
If I can't be with my wife
共度感恩庆祝之时
during a time of thanks and celebration,
为何要有这么多事物又在不断提醒我
why must there be so many constant reminders
那个我无法逃避的现实...
of the inescapable fact that I...
你觉得孤独
You're alone.
我无意不敬
I mean no disrespect.
有你陪伴对我来说意义重大
Your company holds the greatest value to me.
克兰
Crane...
你有权恼怒
you have a right to be angry.
你比任何人失去的都多
You've lost more than anyone ever should.
再说了  若不能发泄烦恼还要节假日干什么
Besides, what are holidays for if not airing our grievances?
婚礼过后
After our nuptials,
我对我们将共度的人生充满希望
I had such hope for the life Katrina and I were to share.
过去这几周过得太疯狂
It's been a crazy few weeks.
休息一晚就会好很多
You'll feel better after a night off.
克兰  米尔斯
Crane, Mills--
有东西给你们看
got something for you.
要是哪晚能休息告诉我一声
Kindly inform me when that night arrives.
休息时间到此结束
So much for the proper allowance of time.
莉娜・吉尔伯特
Lena Gilbert--
慈善家  作家  社会名媛
philanthropist, author, socialite.
吉尔伯特小姐的血统能追溯到
Miss Gilbert's lineage goes back generations,
国父那一代
to the Founding Fathers.
即使她穿着化妆舞会的服饰也非常美丽
She looks great in fancy dresses, too.
我们怎么对她感兴趣了
Why is she our concern?
两天前
That was two days ago.
她不见踪影
No one has seen her since.
正常来说这不是什么问题  但她昨晚
Normally, not a problem, but she didn't show up
并没出席特区的募捐会
at a fund raiser in DC last night.
大概一小时前  参议院多党派领袖私下
About an hour ago, the Senate Majority Leader
联系我  要我去查探她的下落
contacted me personally to check on her whereabouts.
所以这个亿万富翁失踪的事儿非比寻常
Apparently we're not supposed to lose track of billionaires.
抱歉  我是不是听错了  你说她是...
Sorry-- I'm not mistaken-- you did just say she is a...
亿万富翁  对吗
billionaire, correct?
是的
Yes.
意思就是她有十亿美金吗
Meaning she has a billion... dollars?
那是我那个年代
That's the gross national income
13个殖民地的国民收入总和啊
of all 13 colonies, in my lifetime.
听起来像是一个富婆
Sounds like a rich lady took a wrong turn
在回老家的路上走错道了
on the way to her country home.
这种事儿任何一个其他部门都搞得定
Any of the other units can handle it.
她的一名手下传来了这份副本
A member of her staff faxed this over-- copy of a note
这份莉娜亲笔的笔记是在她桌上发现的
they found in Lena's handwriting on her desk.
那是你妻子的名字  对吧
That's your wife's name, isn't it?
我想你也许会感兴趣的
I thought you might be interested.
好吧  真是个有趣的巧合
Okay, yeah, that's an interesting coincidence,
但她不是应该在华盛顿特区混吗  我们怎么能知道
but if she's supposed to be in DC, how do we even know
她失踪后是否还在那附近
that she is still in the area?
她助手用全球定位系统追踪了她的车
Her assistant tracked the GPS on her car.
最后一次是出现在断头谷  之后...
The last ping was here in Sleepy Hollow. After that...
便从地图上消失了
fell off the map, disappeared.
保持联系
Keep me posted.
可能不是同一个卡特里娜
It could be a different Katrina.
上面写得不仅是卡特里娜
It's not just Katrina.
而是卡特里娜・C  就是卡特里娜・克兰
"Katrina C.," As in "Katrina Crane."
一个大写字母而已  说明不了问题的
One initial does not a connection make.
你现在才意识到吗  女中尉
Oh, you've surely come to realize by now, Lieutenant,
咱俩又被牵扯进这件事儿了
that when the two of us are involved,
有这么巧合的事儿吗
rarely is a coincidence a coincidence.
警监说吉尔伯特小姐的血统
The captain said Miss Gilbert's lineage
能追溯到国父那一代
dates back to the Founding Fathers.
你那神奇的网络
Could your... wondrous Internet
能查到吉尔伯特小姐的先祖吗
perform a search on Miss Gilbert's ancestry?
你要我查些什么
What are we looking for?
查断头谷
Ties to landowners
-这片区域之内的地主们  -好的
- within the confines of the Sleepy Hollow area. - All right.
时间是我那个年代
Dating back to my era.
吉尔伯特
Gilbert.
有了  父亲这边
All right, father's side,
拥有新世界钢铁和杜恩化工集团
ownership of New World Steel, Dune Chemicals...
母亲的娘家姓是...
mother's side, maiden name...
弗雷德里克斯
Fredericks.
拥有不少矿产  还投资了铁路
Owned mining interests, invested in railroads.
似乎他们一度占领了半个东海岸
Seemed like they owned half the Eastern Seaboard at one time.
难怪呢
Of course.
弗雷德里克斯庄园
Fredericks Manor.
以拉克兰・弗雷德里克斯的名字命名
Named for Lachlan Fredericks,
他是个有势力的地主  也是...
influential landowner and charter member
大陆会议的创始人
of the Continental Congress.
毫无疑问  他是个狂热的战争支持者
Needless to say, a keen supporter of the war effort.
我猜他是你的朋友对吧
And, I assume, a friend of yours.
我知道吉尔伯特小姐去哪了
I know where Miss Gilbert went.
我在市政厅查了这块地的地契
I pulled the land title and deed from city hall.
这块地属于几个不同的人
This place has had a few different owners,
但自拉克兰・弗雷德里克斯以后
but no one's actually lived here
很少有人在这长期居住
for more than a few weeks since Lachlan Fredericks.
车里没人
It's empty.
也许在屋里呢
Inside, maybe?
这不可能
It's not possible.
这就是你想来的弗雷德里克斯庄园  对吧
Fredericks Manor-- this is where you wanted to go, right?
确实是
It is indeed.
但这完全根本不像我和卡特里娜
But it hardly resembles the residence
在战争时期到访过的地方
Katrina and I visited during the war.
卡特里娜应邀来这待了几个月
Katrina had been requesting to visit the estate for months.
正好我也有空  就跟着一起来了
Finally, my schedule allowed me to accept an invitation.
那些日子我们过得很愉快
We had such a beautiful day together.
伊卡伯德  是谁邀请了咱们呀
Ichabod, we must find our gracious host.
欢迎来到弗雷德里克斯庄园  我帮您拿外套
Welcome to Fredericks Manor. May I take your coat?
-谢谢  -这个庄园是拉克兰・弗雷德里克斯的
- Thank you. - The manor belonged to Lachlan Fredericks.
我只知道他是个狂热的战争支持者
I knew of him as a dedicated supporter of the war,
华盛顿的挚友
a close friend of Washington's,
但其他的事情我就不知道了
but I had no knowledge of his other causes.
你看  亲爱的  你看到了吗
Look around, my love. What do you see?
他们都是自由身
They're all free.
他们选择在这工作
They choose to work here.
这个庄园就是他们的天堂
This estate is a safe haven.
一个大家寻求避难的地方
A place for anyone seeking refuge.
不是很美好吗
Is that not beautiful?
那里的每一个人  无论何种肤色
Everyone there, regardless of the color of their skin,
都能自由地生活  并且得到拉克伦的保护
was free and guaranteed Lachlan's protection.
那是间避难所
This was a sanctuary.
大多数马诺庄园的访客以前都是奴隶
Most of the Manor's visitors were former slaves.
他们中的许多人仍为拉克伦工作
Many of them remained in Lachlan's employment,
和普通人一样有一份合理的收入
earning a fair wage, as every human should.
我不明白如此美景为何就此落入毁灭
I can't fathom how such beauty fell into such ruin.
不然为什么曾和乔治・克鲁尼约会的名媛
Or why somebody who dated George Clooney
想要买下它呢
would want to buy it.
乔治・克鲁尼是个苏格兰人吗
An... an Irishman?
吉尔伯特小姐
Miss Gilbert?
难以置信
Unbelievable.
我是治安厅的人
Sheriff's Department!
举起双手
Let me see your hands!
立刻举起你的双手
Show me your hands now!
天呐
Lord...
他的脸
His face.
像是被野兽袭击过似的
Looks like some kind of animal attack.
是啊
Mm.
山姆・卡尔温
Sam Calvern.
在私人安保公司工作
Works for a private security company.
我要假设他当时和莉娜一起
I'm gonna assume this guy was with Lena.
女中尉
Lieutenant...
血迹还未干
They're fresh.
看来她是从这里被拖出去的
Looks like she was dragged away from here.
吉尔伯特小姐可能还活着
Miss Gilbert may still be alive.
呼叫C62小队
Charlie-six-two,
请求增派支援
requesting additional units.
62小队  收到吗
Six-two, did you copy?
没有信号
No signal.
我得去外面试试
Gonna try outside.
门突然关上了
Jammed shut.
让我来
Allow me.
肯定有别的出口
There's gotta be another way out of here.
不是吧
This is not happening.
不必大惊小怪
Not to be an alarmist...
我们现在可是在一间闹鬼的房子里
But we're in a damn haunted house.
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译  无头笨熊猫&
Slience
翻译  暴龙蛋&
胖兔纯
翻译 断头欠&
圈圈
翻译 卫老哥&
Roaddog
校对  米小勒&
swears
时间轴   imok&
chance-coco
后期  吉吉
断头谷
第一季  第九集
总监  米小勒&
swears
这些木板卡死了
These boards are stucked fast.
肯定有出口的
That must be an exit.
我是不会留在这的
I am not staying in here.
你明白我在说什么吗
Do you understand what I'm saying to you?
怎么会这样呢
That is not going to happen.
我们被困于此
We're trapped in here.
也许是有原因的
Likely for a reason.
我不确定这间房子想要的是我们
I'm uncertain what this house desires from us,
还是吉尔伯特小姐
or Miss Gilbert.
如果她还活着
If she's still alive,
我想我们最好的办法就是找到她
I assume our best course of action is to locate her
确保她的安全
and ensure her safety.
是的  好计划
Right. Good plan.
你好
Hello?
女中尉
Lieutenant?
你要去哪
Where are you going?
-你看到她了吗  -看到谁
- Did you see her? - Who?
那个女人
The woman.
-她刚刚就在我们面前  -什么女人
- She was right in front of us. - What woman?
好吧
All right.
我们面对过女巫
We've faced witches,
死神的无头骑士
a headless rider of death,
入侵我们梦境的睡魔
a demon who invades our dreams,
我相信我们也能勇敢的面对这次危机
I'm sure we can brave this little crisis.
我跟你说  鬼屋什么的向来吓不倒我
I am saying haunted houses do not work for me.
无论是小时候  现在亦或是以后
Not as a child, not now, not ever.
这是我的准则
There's a line.
她不在这里
She's not here.
我们走吧
Let's move on.
等等
Wait...
英国作家斯威夫特1726年所著的寓言小说
《格利佛游记》
Gulliver's Travels.
斯威夫特写的
Swift.
卡特里娜最爱看的小说
Katrina's favorite novel.
她有本一模一样的书
She owned a copy identical to this.
-那是什么  -是封信
- What is it? - It's a letter.
这本书竟然保持了多年
It survived all these years.
卡特里娜的收信地址
Addressed to Katrina?
是我写给她的
One I wrote to her.
就在我面对无头骑士的那天早上
The morning I faced the Horseman.
我挚爱的卡特里娜
"My beloved.
如果你收到封信
If this missive reaches you,
那就意味着最糟糕的事已经发生
It means the worst has come to pass
我阵亡了
and I have fallen in battle."
我请求华盛顿的副官交付这封信
I had asked Washington's aide-de-camp to deliver it
因为面对无头骑士的任务  牺牲在所难免
should my mission to confront the Horseman prove fatal.
换做是他  也会这么做
Which he would have done,
几天之后
several days later.
在你下葬几天后  她肯定回来过这里
She must have returned here while you were buried.
把我的信放在她最爱的书里吗
And leave my letter in her favorite book?
好像是为了让我找到它
It's as though I was meant to find it.
-我不明白  -我也不明白
- I don't understand. - Me neither.
这事不太对劲
Something's not right about it.
我们得尽快找到这个女人
We gotta find this woman.
吉尔伯特小姐
Miss Gilbert?
我们是治安厅的
Sheriff's Department.
莉娜
Lena?
这里以前不是这样的吗
So it wasn't like this before,
鬼影重重  乌鸦哀鸣
all haunted and with crows?
不是的
No...
在战争激烈时期  这里曾是希望之地
at the height of the war, this was a place of hope,
是善良之所在
a force for good.
当我们最终见到屋主时
When we finally met our host,
发现其充满魅力  热心机智
he was charming, warm, intelligent--
正如华盛顿所说的一样
everything Washington said he'd be.
伊卡伯德・克兰
Ichabod Crane,
我是你最忠实的仰慕者  先生
I am your most ardent admirer, sir.
请容我向你们介绍屋子的女主人
May I present our house matron.
格蕾丝・迪克森夫人  你热心助人的事迹
Mrs. Grace Dixon, your reputation for helping
早已名声远扬
those in need precedes you.
回想起来
In retrospect,
很有可能这间屋子当时也收留了许多
it is very possible that their home was also a refuge
躲避超自然威胁的逃难者
from supernatural threats.
拉克伦和格蕾丝曾提到过邪恶力量
Lachlan and Grace talked of evil.
照目前这地方的情况来看
Considering the state of this place,
很有可能是一些恶魔力量找上了他们
it stands to reason that some demonic force caught up with them,
袭击了这个地方
targeted this place,
将它由避难所变成了一所监狱
turned it from a sanctuary to a prison.
如果有什么人或东西盯上了拉克伦
If someone or something had it out for Lachlan,
很有可能他们也盯上了莱娜
maybe they've had it out for Lena, too.
她是他的后代
She is his descendant.
你可能是对的
You may well be right.
这里有更多吉尔伯特小姐挣扎的痕迹
More evidence of Miss Gilbert's struggle.
你先请
After you.
还是你先吧
I insist.
吉尔伯特小姐
Miss Gilbert?
在壁橱里
The closet.
老天  吉尔伯特小姐  我们是来帮你的
My God. Miss Gilbert, we are here to help you.
没事的  我们会救你出来的
It's ok. We've got you.
不 别这么做
No, don't do that.
克兰
Crane...?
求求你们  你们不明白
Please... you don't understand--
这间房子它有生命
this house is alive!
我们救出你了
We've got you.
这些树根  它们缠住了我
The roots... they dragged me.
-它们不让我离开  -没事了
- They wouldn't let me go. - Here. Shh, shh, shh, shh.
我不知道这是什么东西
I don't know what it was.
没事了  深呼吸
It's okay. Breathe.
-过来坐下  -深呼吸
- Come and sit, come and sit, come and sit. - Breathe.
好了  看着我
All right, look at me.
你好  据我所知
Hello. Now, it's my understanding
你的祖先曾经住在这里
that you are a descendant of the man who lived here,
拉克伦・弗雷德里克斯
Lachlan Fredericks.
他是与我们共享伟大崇高理想的盟友
He was an ally to a great and true cause,
一个我见过最勇敢的人
and as brave a soul as I ever met.
不如我们从这里全身而退
So why don't we honor his memory
以此来纪念他的英灵
by getting out of this nightmare in one piece?
米尔斯  你在哪里
Mills, where are you?
就算是感恩节假期
Just 'cause it's the holidays,
也不代表你可以不报到
doesn't mean you don't have to check in.
听到回我电话  你妹妹在这里
Call me back. Your sister's here.
我正在收拾她那堆烂摊子
I'm dealing with her B.S.
-有人心情不好哦  -简直糟透了
- Someone's in a mood. - Yeah, you have no idea.
你最好把我要的东西带来了
You better have what I asked for.
谢谢相借
Thanks for the loaner.
-是你偷的  -当时我们正在
- You stole that. - We were fighting demons
对抗帮助骑士逃脱的恶魔
that were trying to bust out the Horseman.
场面太混乱了
There was a lot of confusion.
我不记得这些枪都是从哪来的了
I lost track of what gun belongs to where.
我五天前就给你留了信息
I left you that message five days ago.
-我现在不是来了吗  -其它的呢
- I'm here now, aren't I? - The rest?
别浪费我的时间
Come on, don't waste my time.
我以为这是你送我的礼物
I thought it was a gift.
算是为了答谢我救了大家一命
You know, for helping save everyone's ass?
雪茄才是礼物
Cigars are a gift.
珠宝才是礼物
Jewelry is a gift.
或许我是个与众不同的姑娘
Maybe I'm a different kind of girl.
谈话结束了
This conversation is over.
-这么说...  -意思是你可以走了
- So... - As in, you leave.
好吧
Fine.
反正本来也是个蠢透了的主意
It was a stupid idea anyway.
什么事
What?
就是...节日快到了
It's just, it's the holidays...
-所以呢  -没事了  当我没说
- And...? - Nothing. Forget it.
我只是想请大家来吃感恩节晚餐
I was thinking of having people over for Thanksgiving dinner
为了感谢艾比重新接受我
to say thank you to Abbie for taking me in,
而我想 ...
and I thought, you know,
如果你没有别的计划...
if you didn't have plans...
你要下厨吗
You're gonna cook?
我还是会做饭的
I can cook.
那这就是一次普通形式的晚餐
So this is a normal dinner type thing.
你做好火鸡和肉汤  我带一些派过去
You make turkey and gravy, I bring some pie.
-克兰和米尔斯也会去吗  -是的
- Crane and Mills will be there? - Yep.
我们要换换口味做回正常人
We act like normal people for a change.
就一晚上而已  我保证
One night only, I promise.
然后我还会偷你东西的
Then I go back to stealing from you.
-真有趣  -我打扰你们了吗
- That's funny. - Um, am I interrupting?
梅希来了
Macey is here.
我可以待会儿再来
I-I can come back.
不用  这是珍妮・米尔斯
No, no, this is Jenny Mills.
我正准备走呢
And, uh, I was just leaving.
我没想到你会来
Hey, I wasn't expecting you.
我的小豆豆
Aw, my little bean.
肯定还有别的出路
There's gotta be another way out.
还有一个我们没想到的出口
Another exit we haven't thought of yet.
吉尔伯特小姐  你在桌上留了张纸条
Miss Gilbert, you left a note on your desk.
在卡特里娜・C这个名字上画了圈
You'd circled the name "Katrina C."
卡特里娜・克兰
Um... Katrina Crane.
我在18世纪晚期的一份花名册里
I found her name in a registry
发现了她的名字
from the late 1700s.
在这座庄园被废弃之前  她是最后一个
She was the last person who came here for sanctuary
到这寻求庇护的人
before the manor was abandoned.
我叫伊卡伯德・克兰
My name is Ichabod Crane.
卡特里娜是我的
Katrina was my...
亲戚  他跟她是亲戚
...relative. He's related to her.
你是否介意告诉我你在这里干什么
Would you mind telling us what you're doing here?
这个地方一直是家族秘闻
Um, this place has always been a family mystery.
没有人知道这里发生过什么
No one knows what happened to it
也不知道我的曾曾曾祖父拉克伦遭遇了什么
or to my great-great-great- whatever-grandfather Lachlan.
当我找到那本有卡特里娜名字的花名册时
When I found that registry with Katrina on it,
我以为自己也许找到了解开真相的钥匙
I thought maybe I'd found the key to unlocking the truth.
所以我把庄园买了回来并且回到这里
So I bought the manor back and came here,
希望能找到一些答案
hoping something would make sense.
但你依然没有找到任何线索
And yet you've found no clue as to
不知道是什么黑暗力量在控制避难所
what dark force took hold of this refuge?
我只找到了一个传说
Just a legend that Lachlan
说拉克伦不止是坚定的废奴主义者
was more than a passionate abolitionist.
他还跟巫术有关
That he was also involved in witchcraft.
那大概解释了卡特里娜为什么这么想来这里
That might explain why Katrina was so keen to visit this place.
如果你的祖先是一个巫师
If your ancestor was a warlock,
用巫术来保护那些
using witchcraft to protect those
来他的地盘寻求庇护的人
seeking refuge on his property,
那么他也许隶属于我
perhaps he was a member of my...
亲戚的女巫团
relative's coven.
你刚才说"女巫团"吗
Did you just say "Coven"?
卡特里娜是一个女巫
Katrina was a witch,
也是你祖先的密友
and a very dear friend of your forefather's.
我把你从那些树根里救出来时  它们流血了
When I freed you from those roots, they bled.
不管是什么恶毒的生物攻击了这所房子
Whatever malevolent being attacked this house,
打破了拉克伦的保护
triumphing over Lachlan's protections,
它已经感染了这所房子
it has infested the property.
这里发生过可怕的事
Something terrible happened here.
跟卡特里娜有关系
And it had something to do with Katrina.
你的研究里
There must be some answer,
一定有答案
something in your research.
也许吧  但是东西都在纽约啊
Possibly, but all of it's back in New York.
好了  该走了
Okay, it's time to go.
-什么东西  -快点
- What is it? - Quickly.
克兰  后头有些东西
Crane, there was something back there.
有些更大的家伙
Something bigger.
是的我看见了
Yes, I saw.
现在是什么情况
What the hell is it now?
我们不能留在这里
We can't stay here.
你要让我们去哪儿
Where would you have us go?
所有人注意
Everyone...
往前走  我就在你们后面
Go ahead. I'm right behind you.
女中尉  快
Lieutenant, come on!
克兰
Crane!
女中尉  在下面
Lieutenant! Down here!
女中尉
Lieutenant!
退后
Stand back.
把手给我  把手给我
Give me your hand. Give me your hand.
女中尉  把手给我
Lieutenant, give me your hand.
吉尔伯特小姐
Miss Gilbert...
不
Oh, no.
克兰  你在哪儿
Crane? Where are you?
克兰
Crane?
是时候了
It's time.
抱歉
Ex-Excuse me...
真够可以的  米尔斯
That was good, Mills.
跟鬼说话
Talk to the ghost.
不好意思
Excuse me.
借过一下
Coming through.
不好意思
Excuse me.
谢谢
Thank you.
不打个招呼吗
Not gonna say hello?
你在跟我爸爸约会
I mean...you're dating my dad--
胆小怕事可不行
there's no point being a coward about it.
我们迟早要见面
We have to meet at some point.
我没有和你爸爸约会
I'm not dating your dad.
我甚至连喜欢都谈不上
I don't even really like your dad.
我有时候也是
Sometimes me, either.
我叫梅希
Macey.
我叫珍妮
Jenny.
你也太不像警察了
You're so not a cop.
本来就不是
Definitely not.
我姐姐才是
My sister is.
感觉一定不错吧
Must be cool.
有个能罩着自己的姐姐
Having a sister to look out for you like that.
是啊  可能吧
Uh, yeah. Can be.
她这人可不好惹
She's a bit of a hard-ass.
那是你没跟我爸住过
Try growing up with my dad.
说实话  我都不敢想像
Honestly, I can't even imagine.
是啊  现在好些了
Well, you know, it's better now.
他在这里工作  我住在城里
He works here; I live in the city.
他工作总是很忙  所以
The man's always busy, so,
我就不用总是
you know, I don't really have to
对着他那张臭脸了
deal with his BS much of the time.
只有我和妈妈
Just me and my mom.
我能接受的了
I'm cool with that.
我从来没有感受过父爱母爱
I never had much of a mom or dad.
不知道那是什么感觉  不过...
Don't know what it's supposed to be like, but...
你或许该给他个机会
maybe give him a chance.
他也不是个太坏的人
He's not a completely terrible person.
友情提示而已
Just some friendly advice.
我知道这里不是什么浪漫的地方  不过...
I know it's not the most romantic spot, but...
起码没人打扰
it's private.
我会长话短说的  我知道你很忙
I'll make this brief. I know, um, I know you're busy.
你要知道  我和她之间没什么...
Just so you know, there is nothing going on between...
你在自己私人时间做什么不关我的事
Whatever you do on your own time is-is none of my business.
但我关心你作为家长的表现
But how you behave as a parent is.
一个周末  这是从你调任以来
One weekend-- that's all Macey's seen from you
梅希唯一的愿望
since you transferred here.
陪她一个周末
One weekend.
而她听到的永远是"突然有急事"
All she knows is-is "Something came up."
我每天都打电话  辛西娅
I call every day, Cynthia...
你知道吗
You know what?
电话根本没用
It's not working.
当你被派过来的时候...
When you were assigned here...
本该是对大家都好的决定
it was supposed to be better for everyone.
镇子更小  更单纯...
Smaller town, easier...
工作清闲  可以让梅希远离城市的烦扰
workload, a place where Macey can get out of the city.
都是你说的
Your words.
我会补偿她的
I'll make it up to her.
而我看见的只有这小镇的辖区...
All I see is a small-town precinct...
有你从前的十倍大
a tenth of the size of your old one.
在断头谷有什么事情能这么让人头疼
What could possibly be such a challenge in Sleepy Hollow?
辛西娅...
Cynthia...
我知道你不明白
I know it doesn't make sense,
但我在这里的工作至关重要
but the work I'm doing here is important.
好吧  那为什么不能让别人去处理呢
Okay. Well, then why can't you have someone else handle it?
不行
I can't.
-我必须亲自处理  -你听听自己说的
- It has to be me. - Do you hear yourself?
你就想变成这样的父亲吗
Is this the kind of father you want to be?
我在努力  辛西娅
I'm trying, Cynthia.
我想让梅希的情况好转
I want to make things right with Macey.
所以我才搬来这里
That's why I moved here.
发生过的事情  就让它过去
What happened, happened.
我们会一起面对的
And we're dealing with it,
她也在面对  而且做得很好
she's dealing with it, and she's doing well.
但这不是长久之计...
But it won't last...
如果你还在逃避作为一个父亲的责任
if you hide from your responsibilities as a father.
她需要稳定...
She needs stability...
而不是更多的失望
not any more disappointment.
我想不到更委婉的说法了
There's no other way to say this.
我已经...
I had some...
让人起草文件...
papers drawn up...
要求完整的监护权
...demanding full custody.
如果你再爽约
If you cancel
不一起过周末的话  我就会提交法院
one more weekend... I will file.
为了她好
For her sake.
你真的要这么对我吗
You would do that to me?
这不是我的本意
This is not me.
是你逼的  弗兰克
This is you, Frank.
克兰
Crane?
莉娜
Lena?
就快生了
It's coming.
加把劲
Hurry.
越来越痛  她就快生了
The pain is rising. She's close now.
孩子就要出来了
The child is coming.
-求你了  我们安全吗  -你和孩子都很安全
- Please, are we safe? - You and your child are safe.
你只要让这个孩子降临人世就好
All you need to do is bring this life into our world.
我办不到
I can't do it.
看着我
Look at me,
克兰夫人
Mrs. Crane.
我办不到
I can't do this,
-除非伊卡博德陪着我  -你必须生下来
- not without Ichabod. - You have to.
为了你自己
For your sake
也是为了孩子
and the child's, hmm?
深呼吸
Now, breathe.
就是这样
That's it!
That's it.
你做得很好
You're doing beautifully.
用力  用力  卡特里娜
Now push... push, Katrina!
用力
Push!
很好  就是这样  拿条毯子来
Good. That's it. A blanket.
快生了
The baby's coming. Now...
用力
Strength, now.
Push!
很好  就是这样
Good. That's it.
克兰夫人
Mrs. Crane...
是个男孩
it's a boy.
我有儿子了
I have a son.
女中尉  嘘
Lieutenant, shh, shh, shh.
这边
This way.
发生什么了
What happened to you?
-莱娜呢  -怪物把她带走了
- Where is Lena? - The creature took her.
把她像玩具一样拖走了
Dragged her away like a toy.
我无法阻止他
I couldn't stop him.
很显然那个怪物不仅仅是
Obviously, the creature is more than simply an agent
-来搞破坏的  -克兰  我有事跟你说
- of destruction. - Crane, I need to tell you something.
-他在这里出没是有原因的  -克兰
- He infested this place for a reason. - Crane...
克兰
Crane...
这是针对拉克伦的蓄意袭击
This was an attack, aimed at Lachlan,
我还不清楚他是不是卡特里娜的盟友
who I'm not certain is in league with Katrina,
-或是她女巫团的成员  -是卡特里娜
- perhaps even a part of her coven... - It was Katrina.
-超自然力量  -我看到卡特里娜生孩子了
- supernatural powers... - I saw Katrina giving birth.
只是...
..Just...
你说什么
What did you say?
在楼下
Downstairs.
我看到了幻象
I had a vision.
我看到这里发生的事了
I saw what happened here.
卡特里娜回来
Katrina came back here
是因为她要生孩子
because she was going to have a baby.
不
No.
不  你肯定是搞错了
No, I'm sorry, you must be mistaken.
她要生孩子肯定会告诉我的
She would have told me.
或者是她需要将此事保密
Or she needed to keep it secret.
如果拉克伦真的是卡特里娜女巫团的成员
If Lachlan was really part of Katrina's coven,
那她来这里生孩子就讲得通了
it would have made sense for her to come here and give birth.
-我很担心  -快点  扶她进屋
- ...I'm afraid. - Hurry, get her inside.
那她就会知道他施在这里的
She would have figured the protective hex he placed
法术...会保护她
on the property... would keep her
还有你的孩子
and your baby safe.
男孩还是女孩
What was it?
那个孩子
The baby.
是个男孩
It was a son.
你有过一个儿子
You had a son.
克兰  还有别的事
Crane, there's more.
生产期间发生了一些事
Something happened during the birth.
发生了什么
What happened?
伊卡伯德肯定会非常高兴的  卡特琳娜
Ichabod would be... overjoyed, Katrina.
拉克伦  怎么回事
Lachlan, what's going on?
他们打破保护这里的咒语了
They've broken through the protections.
有东西来抓孩子
Something came after the baby,
它生长在庄园内部从而打破咒语
beating the hex by growing inside the property.
那个怪物  这栋房子里的恶魔
That creature, the evil in this house,
在你的孩子一出世时便袭击了这里
attacked the moment your child was brought into this world.
拉克伦竭尽全力来保护他们
Lachlan did everything he could to protect them.
拉克伦知道怪物是摩洛克派来的
Lachlan knew this creature had to be sent by Moloch.
带他们走  用我的马车  快走
Take them now. Use my personal carriage. Go.
艾比
Abbie...
我儿子后来怎么样了
What happened to my son?
告诉我
Please.
我需要知道
I need to know.
我不知道
I don't know.
我看到的都跟你说了
That's all I saw.
那他就有可能活下来
Then he could have survived.
他们两个可能都逃过了一劫
They both could have escaped the creature.
克兰
Crane...
吉尔伯特小姐  你没事吧
Miss Gilbert, are you all right?
不
No...
吉尔伯特小姐
Miss Gilbert!
-吉尔伯特小姐  -我无法瞄准
- Miss Gilbert! - Can't get a clean shot!
快跑  快跑
Go! Go! Run!
她去哪里了
Where did she go?
我不知道
I don't know.
女中尉  树根
Lieutenant... the roots!
他能感觉到
He's felt it!
我们怎么逃出去
How do we escape?
这边
This way.
中尉
Lieutenant!
这边  我找到出路了
This way!I found a way out.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
你跟吉尔伯特小姐一起
Stay with Miss Gilbert.
我在这边还有事未了
My business here isn't finished.
-克兰...  -那东西袭击了我儿子
- Crane... - That thing came after my son!
听我说  我们会搞定这东西的
Listen to me-- we're gonna make this thing right.
-但你必须要跟我一起  -保护好她
- You just have to stay with me! - Keep her safe.
-克兰  -听好
- Crane! - Heed my words.
别跟着我
Do not follow me.
我知道你侍奉谁
I know who you serve.
也知道你为什么来这里
I know why you came here.
你以为你可以
Did you think you could
袭击我爱的人而不必承担后果吗
attack those I love without consequence?!
你以为你可以来袭击我妻子吗
Huh? That you could come for my wife?
还有我的孩子
My child?!
替我向摩洛克问好
Give Moloch my regards.
我的天呐
My God.
现在我想回家了
I should like to go home now.
你在这啊
There you are.
那个  我在想
So, I'm thinking...
你可能正需要珍妮烤的火鸡
Jenny's burnt turkey and gluten-free pumpkin pie
和无谷南瓜饼帮你振奋精神
might be just what you need to lift your spirits.
好吧  这推销工作做得不够好
Okay, it's not the greatest sales pitch.
还有朗姆酒哦
There will be rum.
是你最喜欢的
It's your favorite.
巴贝多最好的琥珀朗姆
Barbadian best amber.
我想如果不是它
I believe I would not have survived
我在福吉谷都撑不过来
Valley Forge without it.
非常感激  米尔斯小姐
I'm much obliged, Miss Mills.
但依我的现状  恐怕我不会是个好酒友
But in my present state, I fear I would not be pleasant company.
你看啊
Look...
并不是所有人的感恩节都很好过
Thanksgiving isn't easy for everyone.
我记得我小时候...
When I was a kid, I remember...
走在大街上  路过邻居家的房子
walking on the street, passing houses on my block,
透过一扇扇窗户
looking in windows,
看到家家户户
seeing people, families,
围坐桌旁  谈笑风生
sitting around tables, laughing,
分享火鸡
carving turkeys.
我就特别羡慕
I was just so envious.
那时那就是我最想要的
I wanted that more than anything.
我在英国...也有过
I had it... in England.
我父亲放假期间
During my father's holidays
那时他在牛津大学执教
from teaching at Oxford,
我就坐在壁炉旁
I would sit by the hearth,
而他会以古希腊的辉煌传说
and he'd regale me with glorious tales
款待我
of ancient Greece.
而那时我真的相信  我会追随他的脚步
And I really believed I'd follow his footsteps...
凭己所能  成为一位教授
I'd be a professor in my own right,
而他对我的自豪
yet upheld
会一直支撑着我
by his pride for me.
然后有一天
And that one day,
我会有个儿子
I would have a son,
我会跟他分享同一份
and I'd share that same comfort
让我深觉自由的舒适
that I felt so freely.
我想这就是重点所在吧
I'm guess that's what the point of this is?
反思之时
The time for reflection.
你会看到自己现在拥有的
You see what you have now,
然后你会拥抱眼下
and you embrace what's in front of you.
我险些忘了
Oh, I nearly forgot.
这个是下午到的  给你的
This arrived for you this afternoon.
也许是更多来自亚马逊的宝贝
More treasures from the Amazon, perhaps.
收件人  艾比・米尔斯
寄件人  莉娜・吉尔伯特
莉娜・吉尔伯特寄来的
It's from Lena Gilbert.
弗雷德里克斯庄园多年来的记录
The records from Fredericks Manor throughout the years.
庄园管家格蕾丝・迪克森夫人的
Documentation on Mrs. Grace Dixon--
文件资料
the manor's house matron.
她的后代列表
A list of her progeny.
家谱
Family tree.
洛丽・罗伯茨
Lori Roberts.
我母亲
My mother.
你是格蕾丝・迪克森的后代
You're a descendant of Grace Dixon.
我的祖先带你儿子来到了这个世上
My ancestor brought your son into this world.
英勇非凡
Quite heroically.
我看到了家族类似性
I see the family resemblance.
看来你和我...
It seems that you and I...
我们的命运从很久以前就密不可分了
our paths were intertwined from the very start.
绝对是这样
It definitely would seem.
我们喝一杯吧
We have a drink.
今天是个感恩的日子
It's a day of giving thanks.
致家人
To family.
致找到家人
To finding family.